http://www.viewtier.com/privacy_policy.htm

Privacy Policy
At Parabuild CI, we respect your privacy. We will not sell, share, or rent any data collected on our site to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
Personal Information
Parabuild CI collects basic personal information when you fill out the contact forms or subscribe to our mailing list or newsletter. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest or reply to a query. Such personal information is stored on Parabuild CI computers and is accessed by authorized personnel only. If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, the only required information is email address; all other information is optional.
Server Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. The log files are deleted on a monthly basis.
Software
The software distributed on our site doesn't collect any personal information or send any information to our servers. Any outbound network connections made by our software are made for the sole purpose of performing documented tasks, such as contacting your DNS servers for resolving DTD host names for obtaining necessary records. We don't and never will distribute spyware. We encourage you to download our software directly from our site to avoid potential security risks, such as downloading infected software.
Home |
Downloads |
Sources |
Documentation |
Support |
Customers |
About Us |
RSS |
Privacy policy.
Trademarks. Comments or suggestions? Contact
webmaster@parabuildci.org
